

# **Marcos Vila Obarrio**

## Fullstack Developer | Business Manager

Hello, my name is Marcos. I am 26 years old. I graduated in Business Administration and worked in the finance area for 5 years. My last experience was at Price Waterhouse Coopers. During that process, I learned to work in a team, adapt and be reliable. Today, I want to learn from a good boss in the world of web/app development.

## **Contact Info**

+541155252721

marcosvila96@gmail.com

bit.ly/marcosvilaobarrio

#### **Education**

soyHENRY

2022

**Universidad Catolica Argentina** 

2016 - 2021

San Juan El Precursor High School

2001 - 2014

## **Hard Skills**

**Front End Development** 

React.js | HTML5 | CSS | Redux

**Back End Development** 

Express | Node.js | MySQL

**Soft Skills** 

Reliable | Focus | Teamwork | Funny

# **Work Experience**

Tax Specialist - Price Waterhouse Coopers jan 2021 - dec 2021

Management of accounting balances.

Data entry to the database.

Remote meetings with foreign accountants.

English classes

Financial Advisor - Coswell

feb 2020 - nov 2020

Complete risk analyses.

Contact client to report about news and portfolio.

Year planning for investment solutions.

Commercial Assistant - MAKRO

mar 2019 - nov 2021

Price lists, excel management and email.

Negotiation with suppliers. Stock maintenance.

## **For More Information**



This Barcode Redirect to My Personal Website bit.ly/marcosvilaobarrio